ADINA COATNEY

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER / DESIGNER

About

Hi! My name is Adina Coatney and I'm a Frontend Web Developer and Designer. Most of my experience creating websites have been for non-profit organizations. I enjoy advocating for marginalized communities and harbor a deep passion to change the world wide web to a more accessible experience for everyone.

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Jquery, Scss, React, Git, Github, WordPress, Elementor, Photoshop

Education

2015 | Chanute High School **High School Diploma** 2015 | Neosho County Community College Some College



adinacoatney@outlook.com



adinacoatney.dev

Work Experience

K-Loan | 2020 - Present

Website Management/ Marketing

- Website Management (Wordpress)
- Social Media Management
- Marketing Assistance

Southeast Kansas Independent Living | 2020 - Present

Assistant to CEO

- Diversity Team Leader
- Social Media Manager
- Hiring Team
- Website Management (WordPress)

Grenevision Group | 2016 -2020

Optometric Technician

- Scheduling with EHR/EMR
- Certified Ophthalmic Scribe
- Preliminary Testing

Certificates

November 2021 NuCamp Bootcamp HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

March 2021 NuCamp Bootcamp Bootstrap, SASS, jQuery, NPM, Github